Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1998-1999; Accession ARCH-2001-164
  - Athletics, Dept of, 9/1/98-1/13/99; AA 4.1.30 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 1/14/99-8/25/99 (Box 2)
  - Football Games, Tyrone Willingham - Rose Bowl, etc., 9/8/98-8/11/99; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 2)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 10/8/98-6/14/99; AA 4.1.32 (Box 2)
  - Physics, Dept of, 10/13/98-8/2/99; AA 4.1.33 (Box 2)
  - Political Science Department, 10/5/98-8/25/99; AA 4.1.34 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Center for Research on Economic Dev & Policy (previously Food Research Institute), 9/11/98-2/22/99; AA 4.1.48 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/1/98-6/22/99; AA 4.2 (Box 2)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 9/10/98-6/23/99; AA 4.3 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, 9/1/98-8/12/99; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Education, School of, 10/13/98-8/24/99; AA 4.5 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 9/2/98-2/8/99; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 2/12/99-3/25/99 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 4/2/99-8/27/99 (Box 2)
  - Sweden Stuff related to Learning Lab, 9/11/98-7/9/99; AA 4.10.4 (Box 2)
  - Center for International Security and Cooperation (formerly known as CISAC), 9/24/98-8/99 (Year end report); AA 4.10.6 (Box 2)
  - Center for Latin American Studies, 10/27/98-8/31/99; AA 4.11 (Box 2)
  - Center for Russian & East European Studies, AA 4.11.1 (Box 2)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 2/12/99 - 8/31/99; AA 4.12 (Box 3)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 10/8/98 - 2/10/99 (Box 3)
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, 12/14/98 - 1/20/99; AA 4.14.1 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 11/4/98 - 6/9/99; AA 4.15 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 9/14/98 - 10/30/98 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 5/10/99 - 8/25/99 (Box 3)
  - Law School, 3/2/99 - 5/3/99 (Box 3)
  - Information Technology Service (ITS), 9/18/98 - 8/31/99; AA 4.22 (Box 3)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 9/30/98 - 8/1/99; AA 5 (Box 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 9/28/98 - 6/11/99; AA 5.2 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Scholars, 10/26/98 - 4/30/99; AA 5.3 (Box 3)
  - Sterling, Wallace Award, AA 5.5 (Box 3)
  - Gold Spike Award (for outstanding volunteers), 3/3/99 - 6/16/99; AA 5.26 (Box 3)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 9/11/98 - 8/1/99; AA 6 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 10/1/98 - 6/25/99; AA 8 (Box 3)
  - Fullbright Fellowship/Scholarship, 4/7/99 Only; AA 8.16 (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 4/9/99 - 5/10/99; AA 8.17 (Box 3)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 9/1/98 - 8/26/99; AA 8.25 (Box 3)
  - Terman Fellowship, 9/28/98 - 6/9/99; AA 8.30 (Box 3)
  - Tanner Fellowship, 9/14/98 - 8/22/99; AA 9.19 (Box 3)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, 9/8/98 - 8/26/99; AA 10 (Box 3)
  - Stanford, Miscelleneous, Stanfordiana, 9/15/98 - 6/2/99; AD 1 (Box 3)
  - Historical Society, Stanford, 1/11/99 - 8/9/99; AD 1.2 (Box 3)
  - ROTC, 6/7/99 only; AD 2.26 (Box 3)
  - Honor Code/Fundamental Standard, 9/28/99 - 6/4/99; AD 3.10 (Box 3)
  - President's Office, 9/1/97-8/31/99; AD 4.0 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Lecture Symposium Human & Arts (PLSHA), 9/7/98 - 8/31/99; AD 4.2 (Box 4)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, 9/21/98 - 6/15/99; AD 4.7 (Box 4)
  - University Cabinet, 9/17/98 - 7/30/99; AD 4.13 (Box 4)
  - General Counsel, 9/2/98 - 8/26/99; AD 4.19 (Box 4)
  - General Correspondences, 9/2/98 - 6/4/99; AD 4.20 (Box 4)
  - News Clippings, 1/10/99 only; AD 4.20.1 (Box 4)
  - Condolence Letters, 9/14/98 - 8/11/99; AD 4.20.2 (Box 4)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 12/18/98 - 6/23/99; AD 4.20.3 (Box 4)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 9/21/98 - 7/30/99; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 4)
  - Invitations, 9/3/98 - 1/4/99; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 4)
  - Invitations, 1/8/99 - 10/4/99 (Box 4)
  - Casper's Resignation, AD 4.20.4/3 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 9/4/98 - 12/21/98; AD 4.20.5 (Box 4)
  - Nonsense, 1/4/99 - 9/7/99 (Box 4)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 9/22/98 - 12/15/98; AD 4.20.6 (Box 4)
  - Routine Recommendation Letters (search letters), 12/16/98 - 8/5/99 (Box 4)
  - Recommendations Letters (Students), AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 4)
  - Complaint Letters, 11/12/98 - 5/5/99; AD 4.20.7 (Box 4)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 12/2/98 - 6/7/99; AD 4.20.8 (Box 5)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 9/1/98 - 11/27/98 (Box 5)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 5/24/99 - 8/7/99 (Box 5)
  - Solicitation Letters (General), 2/26/99 - 5/12/99 (Box 5)
  - University Communications, 9/17/98 - 8/20/99; AD 4.22 (Box 5)
  - Office of Campus Relations, 9/8/98 - 11/24/98; AD 6 (Box 5)
  - Office of Campus Relations, 1/14/99 - 8/3/99 (Box 5)
  - Admissions, 9/4/98 - 7/16/99; AD 8.1 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 9/14/98 - 3/30/99; AD 8.8 (Box 5)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of, 4/9/99 - 8/23/99 (Box 5)
  - Cowell Student Health Center, 10/15/98-3/10/99; AD 8.9 (Box 5)
  - Stanford in Washington D.C., 10/2/98-12/23/98; AD 8.10.1 (Box 5)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, 9/9/98-8/26/99; AD 8.11 (Box 5)
  - Financial Aid, 9/1/98-1/28/99; AD 8.12 (Box 6)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 10/19/98-8/25/99; AD 8.18 (Box 6)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 4/9/99-4/27/99; AD 8.18.2 (Box 6)
  - Lake House, AD 8.18.3 (Box 6)
  - Buck Estate, AD 8.18.4 (Box 6)
  - Housing/Dining Services-Students, 9/11/97 - 8/29/98; AD 8.18.11 (Box 6)
  - Residential Education, 9/2/98 - 8/8/99; AD 8.18.13 (Box 6)
  - Registrar - Bursar, 7/24/98 - 7/7/99; AD 8.21 (Box 6)
  - Multi-Cultural Development, AD 9.6 (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action, Student, 12/8/98 - 1/28/99; AD 9.6.3 (Box 6)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 9/10/98 - 8/31/99; AD 10 (Box 6)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests, 9/1/98 - 7/14/99; AD 10.1 (Box 6)
  - Committee for Art, 11/6/98 - 12/15/98; AD 10.7.4 (Box 6)
  - United Stanford Employees (USE), AD 10.7.8 (Box 6)
  - Grievances - Student, 12/2/98 - 5/7/99; AD 10.8.10/3 (Box 6)
  - Retirement, 10/8/98 - 1/12/99; AD 10.8.17 (Box 6)
  - Salaries, 11/30/98 - 6/17/99; AD 10.8.19 (Box 6)
  - Operations and Maintenance, 10/2/98 - 7/4/99; AD 11.4 (Box 6)
  - Environmental Safety Facility, 11/24/98 - 6/18/99; AD 11.4.1 (Box 6)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 9/14/98 - 5/10/99; AD 11.6 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Events, 9/22/98 - 7/29/99; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 6)
  - Lively Arts at Stanford, 9/14/98 - 7/21/99; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 6)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 9/1/98 - 8/24/99; AD 11.7.7 (Box 6)
  - Media - All Forms - External, 10/2/98 - 8/30/99; AD 11.8 (Box 6)
  - Stanford University Press, 10/7/97 - 10/15/98; AD 11.8.9 (Box 6)
  - Stanford University Press, 11/6/98 - 8/25/99 (Box 6)
  - Surveys, Studies, Questionnaires, 10/1/98 - 6/9/99; AD 11.8.10 (Box 6)
  - Media, Internal, 9/14/98 - 7/29/99; AD 11.8.11 (Box 6)
  - Business and Finance, 9/30/98 - 8/31/99; AD 12.2 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Resources, 9/3/98 - 8/3/99; AD 12.2/3 (Box 7)
  - Stanford Management Company, 9/3/98 - 8/24/99; AD 12.3 (Box 7)
  - Internal Auditing, 9/18/98 - 2/24/99; AD 12.4 (Box 7)
  - Internal Auditing, 3/8/99 - 7/26/99 (Box 7)
  - Budget (Budget Group), 9/8/98 - 2/12/99; AD 12.5 (Box 7)
  - Tuition, 10/7/98 - 2/18/99; AD 12.5.4 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, 1/29/98 (Faculty Teaching Activity Reports); AD 12.6 (Box 7)
  - Institutional Planning: Geoff Cox, 9/4/98 - 8/31/99 (Box 7)
  - Insurance, Risk Management, 9/21/98 - 8/27/99; AD 12.8 (Box 7)
  - Vice President for Development, 11/6/98 - 8/19/99; AD 12.10 (Box 7)
  - Office of Development, 7/24/98 - 7/21/99; AD 12.10.1 (Box 7)
  - President Discretionary Allocation, 12/21/98 - 12/22/98; AD 12.10.2 (Box 7)
  - Student Fund Raising, 10/8/98 - 4/19/99; AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 7)
  - President's Fund, 9/3/98 - 8/3/99; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 7)
  - The Stanford Fund, 9/3/98 - 8/31/99; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 7)
  - Matching Gifts, 10/6/98 - 6/24/99; AD 12.10.2/4 (Box 7)
  - Development, Events, 10/13/98 - 8/5/99; AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 7)
  - Donor Relations, 9/16/98 - 8/23/99; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 8)
  - Asian Relations, General, 9/3/98 - 3/11/99; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 8)
  - Asian Relations, General, 7/30/99 - 8/26/99 (Box 8)
  - Technology Licensing/Patents/Copyrights, 9/14/98 - 6/22/99; AD 12.11 (Box 8)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 9/3/98 -1/27/99; AD 12.14 (Box 8)
  - Land and Buildings, General catch all, 2/2/99 - 8/13/99 (Box 8)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues, 8/27/98 - 2/2/99; AD 12.14.1 (Box 8)
  - Housing, Land and Building Issues, 2/3/99 - 4/14/99 (Box 8)
  - Art Gallery & Museums, 6/18/98 - 3/22/99; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 8)
  - Bookstore, Stanford, 11/11/98 - 7/23/99; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 8)
  - Facilities / Planning / Univ. Architect, 8/20/98 - 8/11/99; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8)
  - Faculty Club, 10/22/98 only; AD 12.14.7/30 (Box 8)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Experimental Area (space), 9/25/98 - 6/29/99; AD 12.14.7/43 (Box 8)
  - Memorial Church, 9/18/98 - 6/20/99; AD 12.14.7/50 (Box 8)
  - Parking/Transportation, 9/22/98 - 11/28/98; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 8)
  - Tressider Memorial Union (TMU), 2/9/99 only; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 8)
  - Visitors to campus, 10/1/98 - 8/11/99; AD 13.10 (Box 8)
  - Visitors to campus 96-97 also archived, 9/13/96 - 8/14/97 (Box 8)
  - Conferences, Misc., 11/24/98 - 6/3/99; AD 13.10.1 (Box 8)
  - Industrial Relations, 10/27/98 - 4/22/99; AD 15 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Relations, 10/11/98 - 6/21/99; AL 1 (Box 8)
  - Parent's Club (formerly known as "Mother's Club"), 10/29/98 - 7/29/99; AL 1.1/1 (Box 8)
  - Alumni Correspondence (General - Not Parent/Student), 9/1/98 - 8/23/99; AL 1.3 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Letter Campaign/ Stanford Magazine Classnote, AL 1.3.1 (Box 9)
  - Annual Graduate Mailing, 9/1/98 - 8/31/99; AL 1.4 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Conference/Homecoming, 10/7/98 - 7/26/99; AL 1.7 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Association, 9/30/98 - 7/30/99; AL 3 (Box 9)
  - SAA - 2000 (Stanford Alumni Association), 9/1/98 - 8/30/99; AL 3.1 (Box 9)
  - Alumni Giving (OOD), 2/22/99 - 8/11/99; AL 5 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/1/98 - 8/31/99; B 1 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees Appointments, 9/9/98 - 5/19/99; B 12 (Box 9)
  - Board of Trustees Committees, 9/10/98 - 7/27/99; B 14 (Box 9)
  - Trustee Committee on Land & Use Building Campus Plng, 11/30/98 - 6/2/99; B 14.6 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council, 9/23/98 - 7/7/99; C 1 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 9/4/98 - 12/9/98; C 2 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 4/28/99 - 6/18/99 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Senate, 1/5/99 - 4/15/99 (Box 9)
  - Academic Council - Advisory Board, 9/24/98 - 7/19/99; C 3 (Box 10)
  - Academic Council - Steering Committee - STC, C 4.1 (Box 10)
  - Commission on Technology in Teaching and Learning, 9/17/98 - 3/19/99; C 5.7.2 (Box 10)
  - University Committees, 7/9/99 only; C 6 (Box 10)
  - Committee of Fifteen, C 6.1 (Box 10)
  - General Gov't Info., 10/29/98 - 6/28/99; G 1 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Center - [Government Misc.], 4/7/99 - 4/25/99; G1 PAC (Box 10)
  - California State Government, 9/15/98 - 8/30/99; G 1.2 (Box 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, G 2.3 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Governmental Relations, 9/11/98 - 8/26/99; G 3 (Box 10)
  - Department of Defense (DoD), 11/3/98 - 7/24/99; G 3.7 (Box 10)
  - Department of Energy (DoE), 11/24/98 only; G 3.7.2 (Box 10)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration (NASA), 12/7/98 - 7/26/99; G 3.7.4 (Box 10)
  - Health & Human Services, Office of Civil Rights, 9/2/98 - 7/28/99; G 3.8.1 (Box 10)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), G 3.8.2 (Box 10)
  - Department of Education, U.S. (USDE), 9/14/98 - 8/31/99; G 3.8.3 (Box 10)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), G 3.18.1 (Box 10)
  - NSF - National Science Foundation, 10/9/98 - 8/12/99; G 3.19 (Box 10)
  - Local Government / Local Business, 11/18/98 - 8/31/99; G 4 (Box 10)
  - Foreign Government Relations, misc., 9/9/98 - 7/1/99; G 5 (Box 10)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 9/3/98 - 7/22/99; G 7 (Box 10)
  - Stanford in Government, 10/23/98 - 7/23/99; G 8 (Box 10)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 9/1/98 - 8/30/99; G 10 (Box 10)
  - United Nations, 12/6/98 - 12/8/98; G 12 (Box 10)
  - Kaiser, SHS 3 (Box 10)
  - Special / Newco/ UCSF, SHS 3 (Box 10)
  - Stanford Health Care Board of Directors [end 1-31-97; use SHS 15], SHS 3 * UCSF (Box 10)
  - Meeting of the Selectors, SHS 3 *UCSF (Box 10)
  - USHC [UCSF-SU Health Care], SHS 15 (Box 10)
  - UCSF-SHC Merger, UCSF/SHC-1 (Box 10)
  - Hospital Auxillary, SHS 1 (Box 10)
  - Administration - Special File on Dr. Kiran Bhatt, SHS 3 (Box 10)
  - Hospital Administration, SHS 3 (Box 10)
  - Hospital Board of Directors, SHS 4 (Box 10)
  - Lucille Salter Packard Children's Hospital, SHS 7 (Box 10)
  - Medical Organizations (Miscellaneous), 2/23/99 - 4/6/99; SHS 8 (Box 10)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 9/15/98 - 6/21/99; SHS 9 (Box 10)
  - Other Affiliated Hospitals, Centers and Clinics, 9/28/98 - 8/27/99; SHS 13 (Box 11)
  - Patient Relations, 9/14/98 - 6/10/99; SHS 14 (Box 11)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 9/8/98 - 8/26/99; M 1 (Box 11)
  - Medical School Development, 9/2/98 - 3/18/99; M 2 (Box 11)
  - Misc. Medical School Departments, 10/12/98 - 6/25/99; M 5 (Box 11)
  - Misc. Ad-Hoc Organizations, 9/2/98 - 8/24/99; O 1 (Box 11)
  - Council of Competitiveness, 9/18/98 - 8/30/99; O 1.2 (Box 11)
  - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 12/1/98 only; O 2.11 (Box 11)
  - Education Groups, 9/9/98 - 1/19/99; O 3 (Box 11)
  - Education Groups, 1/19/99 - 8/3/99 (Box 11)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 5/7/98 - 1/22/99; O 3.1 (Box 11)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Ed. (COFHE), 1/25/99 - 8/11/99 (Box 11)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 9/29/98 - 7/23/99; O 3.2 (Box 11)
  - Consortium of Social Science Association (COSSA), 9/28/98 - 5/5/99; O 3.3 (Box 11)
  - Association Pacific Rim University, 10/12/98 - 8/24/99; O 3.4 (Box 11)
  - American Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 9/1/98 - 7/26/99; O 3.7 (Box 11)
  - American Council on Education, 9/18/98 - 8/30/99; O 3.8 (Box 11)
  - National Assocation of Independent Colleges & Univ., 9/1/98 - 8/16/99; O 3.10 (Box 12)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 10/1/98 - 9/7/99; O 3.25 (Box 12)
  - Aspen Institute, 11/5/98 - 4/20/99; O 3.37 (Box 12)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 9/29/98 - 8/12/99; O 3.38 (Box 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 9/17/98 - 8/15/99; O 3.43 (Box 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 9/11/98 - 10/16/98; O 3.44 (Box 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 10/16/98 - 11/30/98 (Box 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 12/17/98 - 4/27/99 (Box 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 3/8/99 - 3/17/99 (Box 12)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 3/18/99 - 8/26/99 (Box 12)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 9/1/98 - 5/2/99; O 3.47 (Box 12)
  - Pacific Ten Conference (Pac-10), 4/30/99 - 8/16/99 (Box 12)
  - CA Business Higher Education Forum, 9/17/97 - 4/3/98; O 3.56 (Box 12)
  - Athletic Awards Miscellaneous, 4/29/99 - 6/15/99; O 4 (Box 12)
  - Political Groups, Miscellaneous, 1/13/99 - 1/14/99; O 6 (Box 12)
  - Research Organizations, Miscellaneous, 9/16/98 - 8/9/99; O 7 (Box 12)
  - Institute for Civil Injustice - RAND Corporation, 9/17/98 - 10/19/98; O 7.9 (Box 13)
  - University Research Association, 11/2/98 - 7/20/99; O 7.16 (Box 13)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 9/1/98 - 11/30/98; O 8 (Box 13)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 12/1/98 - 2/25/99 (Box 13)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 3/2/99 - 5/11/99 (Box 13)
  - Other Colleges and Universities, 4/30/99 - 8/30/99 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 9/3/98 - 9/25/98; O 8.7 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 10/2/98 - 10/30/98 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 11/9/98 - 11/10/98 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 12/2/98 - 12/31/98 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 1/4/99 - 1/12/99 (Box 13)
  - American Association of Universities, 2/1/99 - 2/26/99; O 8.7 (Continued) (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities, 3/1/99 - 3/30/99 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities, 4/2/99 - 4/26/99 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities, 5/3/99 - 6/2/99 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities, 6/1/99 - 8/6/99 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Universities, 8/6/99 - 8/31/99 (Box 14)
  - Assoc. of Governing Boards of Universities & Colleges (AGB), 11/20/98 only; O 8.8 (Box 14)
  - Assoc. of Independent California Colleges & Univ. (AICCU), 9/4/98 - 8/26/99; O 8.9 (Box 14)
  - Cal Tech, O 8.16 (Box 14)
  - California State Universities, 5/6/99 only; O 8.17 (Box 14)
  - Columbia University, 1/12/99 - 6/16/99; O 8.18 (Box 14)
  - Cornell University, 9/3/98 - 10/7/98; O 8.19 (Box 14)
  - Harvard University, 9/3/98 - 6/7/99; O 8.23 (Box 14)
  - Peking University, 9/24/98 - 8/30/99; O 8.30 (Box 14)
  - Princeton University, 1/22/99 - 8/31/99; O 8.36 (Box 14)
  - Nine Provosts, 10/12/98 - 4/13/99; O 8.39 (Box 14)
  - Univ. of CA (All Campuses), 9/14/98 - 8/30/99\; O 8.43 (Box 14)
  - University of Chicago, 10/12/98 - 7/23/99; O 8.44 (Box 14)
  - University of Michigan, O 8.45 (Box 14)
  - Brigham Young University, O 8.46 (Box 14)
  - University of Oregon, O 8.47 (Box 14)
  - University of Southern California, 11/5/98 - 2/23/99; O 8.49 (Box 14)
  - Western Association of Schools & Colleges (WASC), 9/10/98 - 8/10/99; O 8.52 (Box 14)
  - Yale University, 9/16/98 - 8/24/99; O 8.53 (Box 14)
  - Inaugurations - other schools, 9/4/98 - 8/26/99; O 8.55 (Box 14)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 9/10/98 - 8/30/99; O 11 (Box 15)
  - California Council on Science & Technology, 9/15/98 - 5/5/99; O 12 (Box 15)
  - German American Academic Council Foundation (GAAC), 9/10/98 - 7/14/99; O 14 (Box 15)
  - American Philosophical Society, 9/30/98 - 7/29/99; O 15 (Box 15)
  - German Educational Issues, Gov't Studies, 10/1/98 - 8/27/99; O 17 (Box 15)
  - German Stuff, Misc., 11/2/98 - 8/15/99; O 19 (Box 15)
  - Research Misc., 9/7/98 - 8/16/99; R 0 (Box 15)
  - Sponsored Projects, 9/2/98 - 11/30/98; R 1 (Box 15)
  - Stanford Center for Chicano Research (CSSR), 10/7/98 only; R 1.3 (Box 15)
  - Inst. for Research on Women/Gender (same as CROW), 10/2/98 - 8/17/99; R 1.8 (Box 15)
  - Institute for International Studies (IIS), 9/9/98 - 8/4/99; R 1.12 (Box 15)
  - Bio X Project, 4/14/99 - 8/6/99; R 2 (Box 15)
  - Stanford Leadership Institute, 10/15/98 - 11/23/98; R 7 (Box 15)
  - The Science Coalition, 2/1/99 - 7/14/99; R 8 (Box 15)
  - Students (Misc.), 9/14/98 - 8/30/99; ST 1 (Box 15)
  - Student (Groups), 9/24/98 - 8/19/99; ST 1.1 (Box 15)
  - Ram's Head/Gaeities, 11/18/98 - 1/11/999; ST 1.3 (Box 15)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU), 11/12/98 - 8/11/99; ST 2 (Box 15)
  - Stanford Band, 9/1/98 - 5/24/99; ST 3.4 (Box 15)
  - Bechtel International Center, 9/15/98 - 6/21/99; ST 3.5 (Box 15)
  - Hillel, 10/1/98 - 4/1/99; ST 3.7 (Box 15)
  - KZSU, 5/27/99 - 3/29/99; ST 3.18 (Box 15)
  - Haas Public Service Center (T. Stanton), 9/1/98 - 4/22/99; ST 3.29 (Box 15)
  - Gardner, John - Fellowship, ST 3.29/1 (Box 15)
  - Campus Compact, 12/21/98 - 8/3/99; ST 3.35 (Box 15)
  - ASIA-PACIFIC Scholars Program, 9/4/98 - 5/21/99; ST 7.1 (Box 15)
  - Student/Parent Correspondence, 9/2/98 - 8/21/99; ST 8 (Box 15)
- President's records, 1999-2000; Accession ARCH-2002-228
  - Dean of the Chapel - Academic, AA 1.8 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, AA 1.12 (Box 1)
  - Graduate Students/Studies, Issues, 11/19/99 - 8/19/00; AA 1.13 (Box 1)
  - Emeriti, 9/7/99 - 1/20/00; AA 2.2 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action, Faculty/Staff, 11/20/99 - 8/31/00; AA 2.3.3 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 10/17/99-8/18/00; AA 2.7 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Development (Faculty Affairs, Misc.), 9/22/97 - 6/15/98 (Box 1)
  - Fellows of the University, 3/24/00 (1 Doc); AA 2.9 (Box 1)
  - Teaching & Research Assist/Assoc., 5/16/00 (1Doc); AA 2.11 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Studies/Issues, 8/9/99 - 8/1/00; AA 3 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation Issues / Very General, 11/5/99 - 8/1/99; AA 3.4 (Box 1)
  - US News/World Rpt. Rankings/Ratings, 12/4/98 - 10/31/99; AA 3.5 (Box 1)
  - Ideals/Values (West Culture requirement), AA 3.5.1 (Box 1)
  - Continuing Studies, 1/7/00 (1Doc); AA 3.6 (Box 1)
  - Television, Cable, CH51, etc., 9/2/99 - 8/25/00; AA 3.9.1 (Box 1)
  - Summer Programs, et al, 5/25/00 (1 Doc); AA 3.16 (Box 1)
  - Sophomore Seminars, 9/3/99 - 5/19/00; AA 3.18.2 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 8/31/99 - 4/4/00; AA 4.1 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 4/4/00 - 1/31/00 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 1/14/00 - 10/28/99 (Box 1)
  - School of Humanities & Science, 10/27/99 - 10/2/00 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 10/11/99 - 6/27/00; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1)
  - Applied Physics, Dept of, 11/3/99 - 8/31/00; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1)
  - Art, Dept of, AA 4.1.9 (Box 1)
  - Chemistry, Dept of, AA 4.1.13 (Box 1)
  - Dance, Dept of, AA 4.1.16 (Box 1)
  - Computer Science, Dept of, AA 4.1.17 (Box 1)
  - Drama, Dept of, AA. 4.1.18 (Box 1)
  - Economics, Dept of, AA 4.1.20 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Inst. for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR), AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1)
  - English, Dept of, AA 4.1.21 (Box 1)
  - French & Italian, Dept of, AA 4.1.22 (Box 1)
  - German, Dept of, AA 4.1.24 (Box 1)
  - History, Dept of, 9/2/99 - 7/11/00; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (HMS), AA 4.1.28 (Box 1)
  - Music, Dept of, AA 4.1.29 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 12/14/99 - 8/31/00; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, Dept of, 7/28/99 - 12/10/99 (Box 1)
  - Football Games, Tyrone Willingham - Rose Bowl, etc., 10/21/99 - 5/10/00; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, AA 4.1.32 (Box 2)
  - Physics, Dept of, AA 4.1.33 (Box 2)
  - Political Science Department, AA 4.1.34 (Box 2)
  - Psychology, Dept of, AA 4.1.35 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Center for Research on Economic Dev & Policy (previously Food Research Institute), AA 4.1.48 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/5/99-8/2/00; AA 4.2 (Box 2)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, AA 4.3 (Box 2)
  - Engineering, School of, 9/13/99 - 8/29/00; AA 4.4 (Box 2)
  - Education, School of, 12/20/99 - 12/6/99; AA 4.5 (Box 2)
  - Education, School of, 9/21/99 - 12/20/99 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 2/25/00 - 6/28/00; AA 4.9 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 2/7/00 - 6/12/00 (Box 2)
  - Hoover Institute, 9/13/99 - 1/27/00 (Box 2)
  - Sweden Stuff related to Learning Lab, AA 4.10.4 (Box 2)
  - Center for International Security and Cooperation (formerly known as CISAC), AA 4.10.6 (Box 2)
  - Center for Latin American Studies, AA 4.11 (Box 2)
  - Center for Russian & East European Studies, AA 4.11.1 (Box 2)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 9/8/99 - 9/17/99; AA 4.12 (Box 2)
  - Libraries at Stanford (general catch-all), 9/24/99 - 7/18/00 (Box 2)
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information, AA 4.14.1 (Box 2)
  - Law School, 3/3/00 - 8/31/00; AA 4.15 (Box 2)
  - Law School, 1/31/00 - 3/9/00 (Box 2)
  - Law School, 3/4/99 - 12/23/99 (Box 2)
  - Information Technology Service (ITS), 11/2/99 - 5/29/00; AA 4.22 (Box 2)
  - Awards/Prizes, Misc., 9/20/99 - 7/31/00; AA 5 (Box 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, AA 5.2 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Scholars, AA 5.3 (Box 3)
  - Sterling, Wallace Award, AA 5.5 (Box 3)
  - Gold Spike Award (for outstanding volunteers), AA 5.26 (Box 3)
  - Grants, Scholarships, Misc., 10/6/99 - 8/31/00; AA 6 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships, Misc/General Information, 9/7/99 - 7/21/00; AA 8 (Box 3)
  - Fullbright Fellowship/Scholarship, AA 8.16 (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, AA 8.17 (Box 3)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, AA 8.25 (Box 3)
  - Terman Fellowship, AA 8.30 (Box 3)
  - Tanner Fellowship, AA 9.19 (Box 3)
  - Endowed Chairs/Professorships, Miscellaneous, AA 10 (Box 3)
  - Stanford, Miscelleneous, Stanfordiana, AD 1 (Box 3)
  - Historical Society, Stanford, AD 1.2 (Box 3)
  - ROTC, AD 2.26 (Box 3)
  - Honor Code/Fundamental Standard, 11/24/99 - 5/3/00; AD 3.10 (Box 3)